<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Kumbh Darshan</string>
    <string name="button">Button</string>
    <string name="open">Open</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string name="num">+915322500775</string>
    <string name="add">Kumbh Mela Adhikari Triveni Bhawan, Veni Bandh Daraganj,Prayagraj, Allahabad Uttar Pradesh</string>
    <string name="call">Call</string>
    <string name="email">web.kumbh-up@gov.in</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="Kumbh">Kumbh Mela Contact</string>
    <string name="phone">Phone</string>
    <string name="emai">Email</string>
    <string name="num1">+915322504011</string>
    <string name="emercon">Emergency Contact</string>
    <string name="fire">Fire :  101</string>
    <string name="ambu">Ambulance : 102</string>
    <string name="police">Police : 100</string>
    <string name="disaster">Disaster Emergencies : 108</string>
    <string name="About_dep1_dep2_dep3">   Kumbh Mela ::
    Devlopers:
                                                Abhijeet Biswas
                                                Shrikant Pattawi
                                                  Satish Kumar</string>
    <string name="ques1"><b>1. How to Attend the Kumbh Mela ? </b>\n\n  From a tourist perspective, the Kumbh Mela is an unforgettable -- and daunting -- experience! The sheer number of people there can be off-putting. However, dedicated arrangements are made, especially foreigners. Special tourist camps are set up, providing luxury tents with attached bathrooms, guides, and assistance for excursions. Tight security is also in place.</string>
    <string name="ques4"><b>4. Which are the Nearest Airport for coming to Allahabad Kumbh?</b> \n\n Nearest international airport is Varanasi Airport/Lucknow Airport.  Domestic airport is \'Allahabad Airport\' 20 Km far from Kumbh Area.</string>
    <string name="ques3"><b>3. Which is the perfect time for attaining Kumbh?</b>\n \n  Suggest the best date accordingly. If you wish to attaimn main event than Shahi Snan is the best time but if you will attain any of Shahi Snan you have to stay atleat 04 night because during Shahi Snan all the road will be block 02 day before and it will re open 01 day after of Shahi Snan day.</string>
    <string name="ques2"><b>2. This is Ardh Kumbh then why you are calling it Kumbh?</b>\n \n  Government declared name Kumbh, (Speaking after the release of the Kumbh 2019\'s logo, the chief minister said: , the word \'Ardh\' doesnt gel with the philosophy. So, we would be dropping the word \'Ardh\' and celebrate Kumbh 2019).</string>
    <string name="svbh">SVBH</string>
    <string name="svb">Address: Barrister Mullah Colony, MNNIT Allahabad Campus, Teliarganj, Allahabad, Uttar Pradesh 211002 \n Phone: 084002 57377</string>
</resources>
